NASSER AL HADHRAMI

nalhadhrami167@gmail.com | 995 531 69 | | NIzwa, Ad Dakhiliyah 619

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A motivated and inspired HR specialist, who enjoys being part of a successful and productive team. Ability to face challenges & find solutions. Ability to work very hard, under pressure and develop new ideas that help the continuous improvement of the organization.

SKILLS

- *Technical Skills (Google App, HR system, Share Point)
- *Self Learning
- *Critical Thinking

- *Adaptability
- *Multitaking
- *Strong Communications

WORK HISTORY

Human Resources Specialist / University of Technology and Applied Science - Nizwa - Nizwa, Ad Dakhiliyah / 01.2007 - Current

- Data management responsibilities to include processing workflow changes in HR System, audits of data, and data correction workflows.
- Ability to develop, implement, support, and review all HR department policies, procedures, and systems.
- Coordinating training programs internally with different departments and externally with different trainers.
- Participant in the regular meeting with the head of departments and assistant deans, listen to their voices, provide HR recommendations to leaders, and take follow up actions.
- Provide full-service HR support to different employees and assistant deans.
- Active supporting expatriate staff in public relations for example different variety of visas, resident cards, and visa cancellation.
- Highly participant to implement the department's action plans.
- •Active member in various committees including, Quality Assurance, Self-Assessment group, graduation, and statistical system for higher education.
- Conduct special assignments and projects assigned by the Head of the department and assistant dean for Administrative

and Financial Affairs.

Administrative Clerk / National Private School - Bowsher, Muscat / 08.2006 - 10.2006

Worked as an Administrative Clerk.

EDUCATION

University Of Technology And Applied Science - Nizwa **2013–2015** Bachelor Degree in Human Resources Management.

University Of Technology And Applied Science - Nizwa

2002 – 2006 Diploma Degree in Human Resources Management.

CERTIFICATIONS

- 1- (24/09/2020) Google Meet and Microsoft Team by UTAS
- 2- (20/08/2020) Introduction to Blockchain Technology by Blue Ocean Academy.
- 3- (28/07/2020) The Rebirth of L&D by Blue Ocean Academy.
- 3- (21/07/2020) Can Innovation be the Cure for Business by OSHRM.
- 4- (1/03/2020) HR forum by Vision newspaper.
- 5- (10 12/12/2019) HR, Heart of the Business by OSHRM.
- 6- (02/02/2019) How to create an investment project at Omani Women Association in Bahla.
- 7- (28/01/2019) Creative Thinking at Nizwa University
- 8- (11 15/11/2018) Human Resources Management Strategies at Ministry of Manpower.